Lilliput Group was established in 1993
and is an ISO certified original design manufacturer
specialized in the engineering and manufacturing of electronic and computer related products.
The group has two brands, Lilliput and OWON.
OWON Smart Life is Lilliput's Canadian division
focusing on the design and manufacturing of home energy management systems and smart home devices.
Backed up with a solid technical foundation in embedded computer systems
and by partnering with major industry players
OWON integrates smart energy and IoT technologies into its technology mix
offering both standardized products and customized solutions for utilities
contractors, distributors, as well as home builders.
OWON Smart Energy Solutions successfully integrates
the home energy management and smart home application into one single system
using the smart energy gateway that various communication modules are equipped with
thus integrates the smart meter, smart energy devices
and home automation components into the home area network
and further connects to a cloud
allowing two-way message exchange in between.
With the help of OWON's cloud server and mobile apps
people will be able to monitor and even control their home energy usage away from home.
OWON Smart Test is China's leading producer of digital oscilloscopes for science and technology.
Lilliput Electronics is a leading maker of mini-color LCD
and embedded computer applications in China.
Let's now take a quick tour of the Lilliput engineering and manufacturing facilities.
Lilliput designs multi-layer printed circuit boards
with the latest CAD tools.
Mechanical enclosure or packaging is also designed by this department.
Lilliput's engineers are expert at writing, testing and debugging embedded system software.
Here our engineer is developing and testing software
using the EmberZigBee Alliance certified development system.
Lilliput's factory engineering department
encourages team spirit and collaboration.
When difficult issues are encountered
team members come together to solve those issues.
Lilliput's factory floor layout has been designed
to promote maximum efficiency
while at the same time providing the utmost
comfortable, well-lit and healthy working conditions
for all its employees.
The heart and soul of Lilliput's electronic assembly and production
is its state-of-the-art surface-mounted technology
Panasonic pick-and-place line.
SMT assembly and testing.
Two-hole parts are carefully hand-soldered
using lead-free soldering techniques
and vented air systems.
Lilliput has been a global leader
in the production of touch-sensitive LCD displays
for over a decade.
Our pressurized clean room
with controlled air-scrubbing access
insures the highest quality product production
for years of trouble-free operation.
Lilliput manages two standards-
calibration and incoming inspection laboratories.
These are used to maintain the complete
computerized factory operations.
At the point of final assembly
each and every product Lilliput builds
is actively tested under computer control
and carefully inspected for every detail
by each assembly station operator.
Lilliput's stringent ISO 9002
stressed total quality management
with a zero-defects policy.
The final step for each product
is the engraving of a unique serial number
on the product's enclosure.
Lilliput's tooling fabrication department
produces all of the hard-steel tooling
necessary to put mechanical enclosures
and other injected plastic parts
into production, without the need
to use the service of subcontracting tool
and diproducers.
Lilliput is capable of designing
the most intricate tooling,testing it
in production injection molding machinery
certifying the results to exacting
standards of form and fit parameters.